Guide to the University Photography records, [ca.1989-2001]
University Photography records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
University Photography records, [ca.1989-2001]
4-14-2883
Cornell University. University Photography.
77.4 cubic ft., 12 GB
Photographic prints, slides, and negatives.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Photographs, contact sheets, negatives, and slides depicting students and faculty, buildings, and campus events.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
University Photography was formed in 1989 upon the combination of Photographic Services, Cornell Publications Photography (Visual Services), and the Media Services Photo Section.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Photographs, contact sheets, negatives, and slides depicting students and faculty, buildings, and campus events.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University -- Students.; Cornell University; Cornell University -- Faculty.; Cornell University; Cornell University. Photographic Services.; Cornell University. Photo Section.; Cornell University. Cornell Publications Photography (Visual Services).
Subjects:
Students; Universities and colleges -- Faculty
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Slides (photographs).; Negatives (photographic).; Pictorial works
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Only part of this collection representing faculty photographs is currently processed and represented in the finding aid.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Faculty and staff
CONTAINER LIST
- Faculty and staff
  Includes prints, slides, and negatives. Some files also contain printed matter about the subject.
  - A-B
    - Abowd, John, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Abrams, Barb, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Abrams, Floyd, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Abrams, Meyer Howard, 1966-2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Experts list from 1973, Undated negative
    - Abrams, Robert, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Negatives included
    - Ackerman, John, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Adair, Wendi, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Negatives only
    - Adams, Anne, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Adams, Barbara, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Adams, Barry, 1970-1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Two press releases included
    - Adams, James, 1970, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Adams, James, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Adeeso, Anne, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Adelson, Ellen Gussman, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Adler, Kraig, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Ahl, Frederick M., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Ahner, Beth, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Aiken, Paula, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Ainslie, Carolyn, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Albrecht, Andreas, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Albright, Louis, 1980-2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Alexander, Greg, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Alexander, James, 1992-2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Alexander, Martin, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Allen, Josephine, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Allen, Stuart, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Allman, Warren, 1993-1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Allmendinger, Rick, 1990-2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Alonso, Daniel, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Altshuler, Glen, 1992-1997 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Alvarez, Roy, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Ammons, Archie, 1971-1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      Cornell University News Release 1971, One undated photograph. Negatives included
    - Anbinder, Jeffrey, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Anderson, Ben, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Anderson, Bill, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Anderson, Carol, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Andrade, Maydiane, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Annas, Julia, Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Antczak, Doug, 1985-1998 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Antil, Frederick, 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Apgar, Jean, Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Appel, Max, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Appel, Robert, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Applebee, Glen, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Applewhaite, Eleanor, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Apsel, Alyssa, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Aquadro, Charles, 1993-1998 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Aquino, Wilkens, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Arbel, Avner, 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 49)
      Undated negatives and a photocopy included
    - Argetsinger, Cameron, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Arion, William, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 51)
      Undated photo included
    - Armbeester, Gertrude, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Arms, William, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Armstrong, Elizabeth, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Armstrong, Matthew, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Arntzen, Charles, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 56)
      One undated photograph and negatives sheet. Negatives included.
    - Arroyo, Ciriaco M., 1977-1998 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Ascher, Robert, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Ashcroft, Neil, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 59)
      One undated photograph. Negatives included.
    - Ashdown, Susan, 1991-2002 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Asherby, John, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Assie-Lumumba, N'Dri, 1996-2001 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Ast, Dieter, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Athreya, Krishna, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Atkin, Gret, Undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Atkinson, Ross, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Aubrect, Richard, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Aug, Michael, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Austic, Richard, Undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Austin, William, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 70)
      Other people in photos as well.
    - Avedisian, Thomas, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Avery, Robert, Undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Avery, Rosemary, 1991-1999 (Box 1, Folder 73)
      One photograph undated, negatives included.
    - Awa, Njoko E., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 74)
      Several undated photos
    - Babbish, John, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Bader, William, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Badgely, John, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Badgely, Lya, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Baer, Richard, 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Baeumner, Antje, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Bailey, Graeme, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Baird, Barbara, 1986-2001 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Baker, Shefford, 1997-2003 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Bala, Kavita, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Balcom, Don, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Ball, Barry, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Ballantyne, Joseph, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Ballard, Bruce, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Balliet, Whit, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Bandler, David, Undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Bando, Patricia, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Banks, Harlan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Banks, Ralphaline A., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Barazangi, Muawia, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Barbano, David, 1994-2000 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Barcelo̒, John, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Barker, Randolph, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Barker, Robert, 1981-2003 (Box 1, Folder 98)
      Negatives and two CDs included
    - Barnaba, Eugenia, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Barnnon, Patsy, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Barr, Donald, 1971-1991 (Box 1, Folder 101)
      One undated photograph.
    - Barreiro, Jose, 1990-1996 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Barrows, Joyce, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Barry, Frank, Undated (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Bartch, James, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Barton, R., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Basefsky, Stuart, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Bass, Andrew, 1990-2000 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Bassett, William, 1984-2002 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Bassuk, Nina, Undated (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Batchelder, Terry, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Bathrick, David, 1995-2001 (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Batt, Carl, 1990-2000 (Box 1, Folder 113)
      Photocopy included
    - Battig-Von Wittelsback, Kora, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Battistella, Roger, 1993-1998 (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - Bauer, Sheila, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Bauer, Simon, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Baugher, Sherene, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 118)
      one negative undated
    - Bauman, Dale, 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 119)
      Undated photographs and negatives.
    - Bauman, Tim, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - Baxter, Marilyn, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 121)
    - Beach, Margaret "Peggy", 1993-2001 (Box 1, Folder 122)
    - Beck, Sam, 1991-2002 (Box 1, Folder 123)
      One photograph undated, short biography included
    - Becker, Frank, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 124)
      One sheet of negatives undated
    - Beckles, Lauren, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 125)
    - Bedard, Claire, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 126)
    - Beebe, Janet, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 127)
    - Beer, Steve, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 128)
    - Beghin, Tom, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 129)
    - Beghley, Tadgh, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 130)
    - Beijer, Scott, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 131)
    - Belin, Warren, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 132)
    - Bell, Alan, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 133)
    - Bell, Bradford, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 134)
    - Bell, Dennis, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 135)
    - Bell, Jim, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 136)
    - Bell, Robin, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 137)
    - Bell, Russell, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 138)
    - Bellinder, Robin, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 139)
    - Belnick, Mark A., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 140)
    - Belzer, Mike, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 141)
    - Bem, Daryl, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 142)
      Two sheets of negatives undated
    - Bem, Jeremy, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 143)
    - Beneria, Lourdes, 1986-1996 (Box 1, Folder 144)
      Two photographs undated
    - Benjamin, Kate, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 145)
    - Benson, Fran, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 146)
    - Berens, Don, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 147)
    - Berest, Yuri, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 148)
    - Berg, Elena, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 149)
    - Berkelman, Karl, 1985-1999 (Box 1, Folder 150)
    - Berman-Brandenberg, Judith, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 151)
    - Bernal, Martin, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 152)
      Negatives and photocopy included
    - Bernard, David, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 153)
    - Bernes, Mary, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 154)
    - Berrigan, Daniel, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 155)
    - Berry, John, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 156)
    - Berry, Michelle, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 157)
    - Bertram, John, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 158)
    - Berzon, Marsha S., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 159)
    - Bestor, Ted, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 160)
    - Bethe, Hans, 1967-1976 (Box 1, Folder 161)
      Cornell Newsletters and Photos (riding bike and teaching, black suit chalk board equations) from 1968, Bethe vs. Commoner Debate 1976, Cornell Chronicle Supplement 2005
    - Bethe, Hans, 1981-2005 (Box 1, Folder 162)
      Two sheets undated negatives and one undated photo. Magazine celebrating Bethe's life included.
    - Bhaskaran, Radish, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Bierman, Harold, 1969-1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Bilderback, Don, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Negatives and a business card included
    - Bills, Nelson, 1993-2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Bilson, Malcom, 1981-1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Bird, John, 1997-2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Birman, Ken, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Bishop, Don, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Bishop, John, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Bisogni, Carol, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Bitz, Robert, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Bizzell, Virginia, 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Bjerken, Xak, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Blackler, Antonie, 1966-2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Undated news releases included
    - Blake, Aaron, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Blake, Robert, 1986-1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Blakely, G. Robert, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Blakely, Robert, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Blanchard, Ken and Marjorie, 1985-1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Negatives included.
    - Bland, Robert, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Blankinship, Carmen, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Blau, Francine, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      Negatives and photocopy included.
    - Blissard, Gary, 1995-2001 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Blood, Dick, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Bloom, Art, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Bloomfield, Robert, 1992-2002 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Blumin, Stuart, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Bobruff, David, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Bodenschatz, Eberhard, 1992-2003 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Boehlert, Sherwood L. - USCongressman, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      One photograph undated
    - Boes, Bea, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Bogel, Rick, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Boice, Bill, 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Boissannas, Christian, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Bolanle, Asumi, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      No name on photos
    - Bonney, Rick, Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Booker, Ron, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Boor, Catherine, 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Boothe, Sandy, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Borden, David, 1987-2001 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Bordenet, Ron and Dick, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Bossard, Kermit, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Boudreau, John, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Bowers, John, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      Note included
    - Bowman, Stan, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Bowser, Paul, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Boyd, Gwen, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Boyer, George, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Bretscher, Anthony, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Bricker, Brenda, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Briggs, Vernon, 1988-1995 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Bristow, Barbara, 1996-2003 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Brittain, Charles, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Broadhead, James L., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Brock, Joel, 1990-2002 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Brody, Jane, 1989-2000 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Bronfenbrenner, Kate, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Bronfenbrenner, Urie, 1968-1999 (Box 2, Folder 58)
      Some photos and negatives undated
    - Brouwer, Piet, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Brower, Andrew, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Brown, Bill, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Brown, Dan, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Brown, Jane, 1987-1994 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Brown, Lois, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Brown, Lynn, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Brown, Nancy, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Brown, Tommy, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Browne, Jennifer, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Brownell, Judith, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Brumberg, Joan, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 70)
      Some photos undated. Negatives included.
    - Brunetti, Andrea, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Bruns, Peter, 1992-2000 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Brunson, Roger, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Brutnell, Thomas, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Brutsaert, Wilfried, 1989-1994, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Bruyere, Susanne, 1992-1999 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Bucci, Joanne, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Bunce, Valerie, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Burgenstock, Mary Nell, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Burise, Paul, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Burkhauser, Richard, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 81)
      Negative included
    - Burlitch, James, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Burns, Joe, 1988-2001 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Burr, Sande, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Burt, Robin, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Burtscher, Martin, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Busch, Wendy, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Butler, David, 1993-2001 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Butler, JS, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Butler, Walter Ron, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Byall, Lynne, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Byron, Susan, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - C-D
    - Caban, Pedro, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Cahoon, Richard, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Caldwell, Steven, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Call, David, 1973-1995 (Box 2, Folder 96)
      Undated photographs, negatives included
    - Call, Richard, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Callister, John, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Calnke, Bruce, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Calvo, Joseph, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Campbell, Colin, 1990-1997 (Box 2, Folder 101)
      Some undated photographs. Negatives included
    - Campbell, Don, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Campbell, Joe, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Campbell, Mark, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Campbell, Steve, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Campbell, Steven, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Campbell, Xuan, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Canfield, Rick, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Canina, Linda, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Canterbury, Linda, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Capel, Mike, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Capps, Susan, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Carbone, Larry, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Cardie, Claire, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Carlin, Matt, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Carmichael, Leland, 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Caron, Vicki, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Carpenter, Barry, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Carr, Linda, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Carr, Lisa, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Carrillo, Loretta, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Carter, Jerry, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Carter, Maureen, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Caruana, Richard, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Casasola, Marianella, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 125)
      No photos attached to the photo request of 2004
    - Casella, George, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Cassano, Patricia Ann, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 127)
      Newspaper article included
    - Cassarrett, Allison, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Cassel, David, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 129)
      Negatives only, description of photos included
    - Castillo, Deborah, 1988-1999 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Castillo-Chavez, Carlos, 1989-2002 (Box 2, Folder 131)
      Two photographs undated, negatives included
    - Cathles, Lawrence, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Caughey, Dave, 1977-1989 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Cawley, John, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Ceci, Stephen, 1992-2002 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Cerione, Rick, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Chabot, Brian, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Chandra, Subhash, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Chapman, Duane, 1993-2000 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Chase, Larry, Undated (Box 2, Folder 140)
      Undated negative included
    - Chase, Robert, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Chausen, Tom, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Chen, Joseph, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Chen, Lai Liang, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Chen, Yiyi, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Cherney, Debbie, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Cherney, Jerry, 1994-1998 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Chigurupati, Jay, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Chiment, John, 1985-2000 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Chirik, Paul, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Chiu, Michael, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Chon, Julie, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Christopherson, Susan, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Christy, Ralph, 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Chu, Chih Chang, 1989-1999 (Box 2, Folder 155)
      Undated photograph, negatives, photocopy, and an article included.
    - Chung, Beth, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Churchill, Alice, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - Cima, Joyce, 1972-1998 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Clancey, Paulette, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 159)
      Undated photographs and negatives included
    - Clardy, Andrea, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - Clardy, John, 1979-2001 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Clark, Al, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Clark, Beth, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 163)
    - Clark, Christopher, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - Clark, Laura, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 165)
    - Clark, Tom and Nancy, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 166)
    - Clarke, James, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 167)
    - Clarke, Kenneth, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 168)
    - Clarksberg, Marin, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - Clauel, Pierre, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - Cleese, John, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Clinton, Bill, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Autographed photo
    - Clinton, Hillary, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Set of negatives, and photographs undated
    - Clinton, Hillary, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Clinton, Kevin, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Cluck, Mary, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Coates, Geoff, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Cochran, Moncrieff, 1993-1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Coffin, Bonnie, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Coffman, Charlotte, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Coffman, Ronnie, 1993-2003 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Item from 2003 job order only
    - Cohen, Abby Joseph, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Cohen, Alan, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Cohen, Amber, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Cohen, Claude, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Cohen, Walter, 1988-1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Cohen-Rosenthal, Ed, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Cohn, Abby, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Colavito, Greta, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Cole, Paul, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Coleman, Gould, 1971-1995 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Collins, Lance, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Colucci, Mary Elizabeth, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Combs, Gerald, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Compton, Merritt, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Comstock, Jonathan, 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Concannon, Patrick, 1981-1997 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Conklin, Patricia, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Connelly, Kevin, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Connelly, Robert, 1997-2002 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Constable, Robert, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Cooch, Evan, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Cook, Alice, 1969-1997 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Cooke, Robert J., 1985-1998 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Coons, Bill, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Cooper, Eric, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Coral, Lenore, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Cordes, James, 1993-2002 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Corgel, Jack, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Cornelius, Steve, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      Item from 1991 is a job order
    - Corson, Dale, 1970-1999 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      Undated photograph, negatives and a photocopy included
    - Corson-Rikert, Jane, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Costello, Dick, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Costich, Denise, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Cowdrey, Bill, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Cowen, Edwin, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Cowie, Robert A., 1997 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Cox, Bill, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Cox, Deborah, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Cox, Phil, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Coyle, Anne, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Craft, Harold, 1992-2003 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Craighead, Harold, 1989-2002 (Box 3, Folder 53)
      Undated negative
    - Crames, Michelle, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Crane, Brian, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Crans, Henry, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Creasy, Leroy, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 57)
      File did not provide first name- Found name based on google searsh - please check
    - Cuevas, Francisco, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Cullen, Tom, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Culler, Jonathan, 1993-2001 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Currie, Bruce, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Dacko, Marnie, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Daels, Peter, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Dalton, David, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Daly, Norman D., 1974-1981 (Box 3, Folder 65)
      Undated photographs and negatives. Press release included.
    - D'amato, Alfonse, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - D'andrea, Raffaello, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Danforth, Brian, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Daniel, Cletus, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Daniels, Diana, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Danko, Sheila, 1995-2002 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - D'Aprix, David, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Daub, Keith, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - David, Keith, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Davidson, Rachel, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Davies, Peter, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Davis, Doris, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Davis, Felicia, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Davis, Gregson, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Davis, JC Seamus, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Dawson, Todd, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 81)